red5.co.uk 2013-05-23

# Privacy Policy | RED5 Gadget Shop

## Your Privacy

Protecting the security and privacy of your personal information is important to RED5 and to the way we conduct our business in compliance with laws on privacy, data protection and data security. We at RED5 are also shoppers and customers, so we understand how important privacy and security is. We hope this policy will help you understand what information RED5 may collect, how we use and safeguard that information and with whom we may share it. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you.

## Personal Information

Through our website, RED5 will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address), unless you voluntarily choose to provide it to us (e.g., by registration, or signing up for newsletters or competitions).

When you do provide us with personal information, we usually use it to respond to your inquiry, process your order or provide you access to specific account information. Also, to support our customer relationship with you.

We may also use Personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti fraud checks. Personal Information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity - a credit check is not performed and your credit rating is unaffected.

We may store and process personal information to better understand your business needs and how we can improve our products and services; or

We may use personal information to contact you about any RED5 offers that we think you may be interested in or to conduct online surveys to understand better our customers' needs.

If you choose not to have your personal information used to support our customer relationship (especially direct-marketing or market-research), we will respect your choice. We do not now (and do not intend to) sell, rent or otherwise market your personal information to third parties.

You can choose to opt out of marketing communications at any time in the "My Account" section of our website.

## Cookies and Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically

When you access our website, we may automatically (i.e., not by registration) collect information that is not personally-identifiable (e.g., type of Internet browser and computer operating system used; domain name of the website from which you came; number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed). We may use this information to measure the use of our websites and improve their content.

If you do not wish for us to use cookies when you use the Red5.com website please change your Internet browser settings to not accept cookies. You can find out how to do this by Googling it of course or help tab on your browser. Please note that cookies allow you to take full advantage of the services we provide through the Red5.com website including checkout functionality and so we recommend that you leave them turned on.

Red5 is working towards complaisance with the recently revised e-Privacy Directive and is working with the latest guidance from the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO).

## 3rd Party Ad Serving

We may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our web pages. We do NOT provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites.

## Royal Mail & DPD

We may have to disclose some of the information you provide to service suppliers to help complete your order. These include Royal Mail and DPD. By using our web site you give consent to us to use the personal information you have given RED5 and our trusted partners, as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

Back to Top
